=== FrameByFrame Changelog ===

=== Version 2.0 ===
Rebuilt from the ground up. FBF now handles larger projects, saves documents more carefully, has Core Image filter support... 
The whole shebang. Ha ha, bang.

=== Version 1.10 ===
Bug fixes:
FrameByFrame now produces proper movies for images of any resolution. This means you are no longer restricted to using 72 dpi images.

=== Version 1.9 ===
Bug fixes:
- The shutter sound selection "no sound" now has an effect - it turns the sound off!

New features:
- Norwegian and Brazilian Portuguese localizations.
- Images are now numbered sequentially.


=== Version 1.8 ===
- Improved picture quality through frame averaging. Set up averaging of two to twenty frames in the Preferences.
- "Shutter sound" provides auditory feedback. Select your favorite sound in the Preferences.
- Delete selected pictures using the Back Space key.

=== Version 1.7 ===
- Navigate your movie's pictures using the keyboard.
- Added support for Apple Remote. Use your Mac's remote control to take pictures and navigate them.
- It is now possible to set 0% and 100% onion skinning opacity by clicking the film strip/camera symbols flanking the slider.
- The FrameByFrame newsfeed will inform you of new versions.
- Extended preferences for configuring keyboard shortcuts, remote control use and newsfeed download.
- Added Russian and Ukrainian localizations.
- FrameByFrame is now licensed under the GNU General Public License. See "Help > Licensing" for more information.

=== Version 1.6 ===
- Snapshot key may now be assigned freely using "File > Preferences".
- Added Polish language support.

=== Version 1.5 ===
- Added Japanese language support.
- Added Netherlands language support.

=== Version 1.4 ===
- Improved English language support.
- Added German language support.
- Added Greek language support.
- Added Spanish language support.
- Added Italian language support.

=== Version 1.3 ===
- Redesigned graphical user interface.
- Controls for adjustment of onion skin opacity.
- Copy/paste/cut/delete menu items may now be used.
- Undo/redo mechanism including tracking of document changes and reverting to saved versions.
- Drag and drop behaviour improved (minimum drag distance).
- "Special Thanks" screen.

=== Version 1.2 ===
- Reorder pictures and interact with the Finder using Drag and Drop.
- Importing pictures now puts them in the correct place.
- Documents now have their own icons.
- Now with correct version number.
- Exported QuickTime movies now get „.mov“ extension by default.

=== Version 1.1 ===
- Use any QuickTime codec present on your Mac to encode your movies, including the fabled H.264.
- Encode with high, standard or low quality to adjust the file size of your movie.
- The image strip keeps the focus on the most recently inserted to reduce the amount of scrolling necessary.
- First version compatible with Tiger.

=== Version 1.0 ===
- Happy Birthday!
- All basic features, movie export using MPEG-4 codec.
